ILR School Library Technical Services Files 6121
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Library Technical Services Files
1983-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
6121
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records.
5806216
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 17, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations-- Archives; Martin P. Catherwood Library -- Archives
5806216
- Request for Proposals for an Integrated Library System for Cornell University Libraries (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Retrocon, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Student Assistants (Box 1, Folder 3)
- No Record (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Assembly Minutes (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NOTIS: Terminals Printer Troubleshooting (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Backlogs (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bear Access (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Catherwood Library (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Catherwood Review (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Tech Services Focus GRP (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Planning Group (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Planning Group cont. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Routing (Box 1, Folder 14)
- WWW Grant (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Tech Team (Box 1, Folder 16)
- WWW (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Team Meetings (Box 1, Folder 18)
- NOTIS Technical and User Documentation (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Annex Transfers, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Summer
- Annex, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Statistics, Automated (CTS), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Circulation Implementation T. F., 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  March
- RLG: Reports System, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Authority Cont'l at CUL, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  June - September, 1986
- Time & Backups (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Statistics (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Cataloging Activities, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Cataloging Activities, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Cataloging Activities, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Library Routing List (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Guide to Index Typing (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 10-up Typing Manual (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Guide to Card Typing (Box 2, Folder 16)
- TSEG (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Catalog Unit Reports Annual Cummulation (Box 3, Folder 1)
- RLIN Charges, Accts. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Size, ILR Lib. Collection (Box 3, Folder 3)
- NOTIS GTO 3.0 Installation Instructions (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Invoices (Title IIC) Accts. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Title IIC, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Blackwell N.A. (Title IIC) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- ILR - Title IIC Retrospecitic Conversion Project, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Steering Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Title IIC, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Memos, etc. folder 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Memos, etc. folder 2 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Meeting Minutes (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Faculty Meetings folder 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Faculty Meetings folder 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Faculty Meetings folder 3 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- APPC (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Planning Group (Box 3, Folder 18)